So I'm, I'm just supposed to, I'm trying to understand something.
Zoran Mamdani, who the other day, the other day was being told, you are not the right
candidate for the Democratic Party.
It is too soon.
You need to chill.
So that Zoran then sat down for an interview to say that this other candidate is not acceptable
in the, it's not an acceptable time for him to primary Hakeem Jeffries.
Now here we have hear and say things.
So they don't want to come on live and actually say something though, but they want to hide
behind their little Instagram and say things.
So like this person who just said, I'm dumb as hell with an exclamation point.
I've invited them to come on live.
Let's see.
Are they going to come?
Are they going to come on live so they can tell me what I'm saying is dumb.
I'm trying to understand why anybody here, people are like, they're going to eat you
up for this, et cetera, et cetera.
He did an interview and said this out of his mouth.
What are you all talking about?
This is not something that was said simply, and this was not something that was simply
just reported by the New York Times, which by the way, when it was reported by the New
York Times, I didn't take it as fact because they are a completely co-opted and they're just
an irrelevant rag.
However, when you sit down and do an interview and you say, this is not the right time for
Chiyose to primary Hakeem Jeffries, and then it is reported that you are going to attend
the DSA forum to speak against Chiyose running, explain to me how that is considered above board.
And then when people say, well, he's not perfect, I'm trying to understand why you all's bar for
the people who represent you is so low.
Let me tell you what my version of he's not perfect is.
My version of someone not being perfect is, um, they are in a panic and they, you know,
lose their, um, they lose the handle of their emotions for a moment.
Um, my idea of someone not being perfect is, you know, they're, they're, they, they're like
shitty, they, they, they cancel last minute.
Okay.
They cancel last minute.
My idea of like someone not being perfect is, um, you know, they may not be the best at
responding to texts in a timely fashion.
You all say things like, is it a strategy for a longer game?
And I'm trying to figure out where, what are you watching?
What are you watching?
What long game?
What is the long game?
I think it's even a game at all should really concern you.
And no, he hasn't expressed why this is not the time.
And the reporter didn't ask him, but he shouldn't have had to be asked because he's asserting
it.
So the fact that folks are still being passive is so deeply frustrating to me.
We do not have to be passive, but you all continue to allow yourselves to be bystanders to your
own life.
Then you have people who are like, this is a local election.
Hakeem Jeffries is the literal minority leader of the house of representatives.
This is not just a local election.
He's also one of the greatest recipients of AIPAC funding.
And that's just AIPAC.
There are other Israeli lobbies.
And when he is taking money from these lobbies, he is washing money and he is stealing from
the American public and our tax dollars.
So don't tell me about, oh, this is a local election.
And if it really is a democracy that you all want to believe it is, then why the is Zoram
Amdani even voicing an opinion on who should be primarying Hakeem Jeffries?
This nigga just got the job two days ago.
Two days ago, it feels like.
He has barely been mayor.
Chelsea was riding for Zoram this entire time.
Okay.
So the fact that he would do this is, and then people will say, well, maybe they're holding
it over his head and maybe he's being blackmailed.
You know what?
I guess you all ain't never been in no shit before.
And that's really what it must be.
You just ain't never been in no shit before.
Because if you really are about it person, then you do, you still stand on business.
We Ned Stark over here.
You stand on business.
Your chin is head high.
So I'm trying to understand why your integrity bar is so low.
And it's because your own integrity is low.
And this concept of like the people ain't ready to vote Jeffries out.
Shut up.
Stop with the nonsense.
It literally just said the other day that we weren't ready to vote for Zoram Amdani and
he won.
Do you hear you?
I am begging you to hear yourselves.
I mean, it's just, it's just, it's beyond my scope of comprehension.
It truly is.
And the reality is that the voters don't seem to ever get to say who the hell we're ready
for because you always have Democrats deciding for us and that should piss you off.
It should piss you off.
You all really should be saying, Zoran, how about you shut the heck up and mind your business
of running this city?
How about you do that?
Run the city.
This is completely extracurricular unless you're protecting Israeli lobbyist money.
That's what's happening here.
And anytime you see them repeating the same rhetoric, you know that they have been told
the script.
Him and AOC have been told the script and per usual, they are running in line.
And AOC, she got her whole political career started by Zionist money.
So I wish you all would actually know something before you keep talking because I'm someone
who knows what I'm talking about.
I don't talk about things I don't know about.
Talking about Hakeem being cool, you sound absolutely nuts.
As long as Hakeem ain't a member of the Commonwealth Club, he's cool.
You all don't seem to know anything about Hakeem Jeffries if you're writing for him.
He is not writing for you.
He is a spineless, yellow-bellied, what's the word I'm looking for?
Is callo the word I'm looking for?
Callo?
I think that's the word I'm looking for.
He's callo.
So, Hakeem Jeffries and I'm reading the comments.
No, I don't like any politicians and you shouldn't either.
I support public servants, not politicians.
I support people who speak earnestly and honestly for the people and against the fascism that
is taking place.
I can name two.
I can name two people in local government and I can name one person.
I can name one person in electoral government that I actually like.
Rashida Tlaib and in local government, Dottie Joseph in Miami and Angie for Florida in Jacksonville.
That's it.
Everybody calls him Apec Shakur.
I don't know why you guys didn't know that, but he's been being called that for years.
And, you know, you say things like, let's not pretend like the powers that be in this country will ever accept an ethical leader.
And I think that what you all, what drives me crazy about you all is that you seem to think that this country has existed forever.
And it's weird.
It's weird.
This country does not, this country is like super young.
This country has not been in existence for any long time that you feel like, oh, wow, there's no beginning that happened before that.
What are you talking about?
Like, what are you talking about?
Anybody that is not ardently and earnestly standing against the genocide in Philistine, you should have a problem with.
Anybody that was not defending the First Amendment rights of the students that were protesting at colleges, you should have a problem with.
Anybody that is taking funding from a completely other country, you should have a problem with.
No country is old.
Anyways, like I said, for some reason, there is a very low standard that continues to be pervasive amongst the voting bloc.
You all continue to show why you're in the situation you're in.
One, because you look at people like myself and you say, we are leftists and we're expecting too much.
I know this person is trying to be like really deep, like no country is old.
I get what you're saying, but in the context of what I'm saying, there are countries older than others.
You know that that's what I'm saying, but you want to be this person and contrarian and that's annoying.
So the reality here is that your world is happening to you.
Your world is happening to you.
And you want to be a bystander.
And it's deeply disturbing.
You're saying butchware for governor.
Based on what?
And this person, Maxi Shaw, what do we do?
Have you listened to anything I've said?
If the problem is that you don't have standards for your electoral officials, then wouldn't the thing to do be to have standards?
If the problem isn't that you don't know enough about the history or the way governance works, wouldn't the problem, wouldn't the solution or the thing to do to be to actually get informed about that?
Like, this is where we are.
You want to be told what to do, but you don't want to do anything.
Just to annoy Hakeem Jeffries.
Even if he doesn't win.
The reality is that there has to be actual actions.
There has to be people who will actually do things and step in and exist in ways other people haven't.
I do that every day in my life.
So for you all to not want to see that, for you all to not understand that, but still then say, well, maybe it's the long-term strategy for the Democrats and not understand what the long-term strategy, what the short-term strategy for the people is, is beyond me.
It's beyond me.
Why do you have trust in people that you don't know?
Why do you have more trust in people?
Actually, you know what?
That's not even true.
Why do you have more trust in people who have shown you that they are not trustworthy than you do in yourself?
Why?
I've shown you that they're not trustworthy.
They've demonstrated this over and over and over again.
They have no plan.
Why?
No.
And the only way that you will begin trusting in yourself is if you start learning.
Because confidence only comes from experience.
That's it.
People can influence you.
People can build up your confidence, but only you can actually believe it.
And it comes from evidence.
The best confidence building is when people remind you of what you've already done.
When people remind you of who you are.
When people will remind you of what you know.
They're not building your confidence.
They're just reinforcing the facts.
If you don't have that to stand on, then you're just walking on arrogance.
Inform yourself.
Kill your ego.
Expand your consciousness.
Lean into your imagination.
Stop putting up barriers for possibility.
And allow yourself to be decolonized so that you can become organized.
Because that's a big problem that we have right now.
We do not have enough bodies, enough souls, enough spirits that can be organized.
Because everyone is colonized.
So I'm hoping that you're listening to what I'm saying.
Zoran Mamdani has no place to be telling this brother not to primary that brother.
Especially when he is echoing the sentiments of AOC and the Democrats.
There should be no one of any merit who is defending the possibility of Hakeem Jeffries sitting in that seat any longer.
Every effort should be made to get him out of there.
And Chuck Schumer at that.
Have a good night.
And buy my book.
It's available at amandaseals.com.